FROM ME TO YOU: KIMI NI TODOKE
3RD SEASON
- Good morning!
- It's been a while!
- How was summer break?
- I had way too much fun!
It's the start
of the second term.
And for a second-year, that means...
Our class trip's soon! Okinawa!
I can't wait. It's gonna be my first time.
- Yeah, same for me.
- Same here.
Gotta avoid the UV rays.
So, hey. When it's November here,
what month is it in Okinawa?
It's also November.
What?! No way!
Chizu, turn it down a notch, okay?
If I can't get pumped now,
then when am I allowed to, huh?
I'm so sorry about that.
Are you all right?
It's okay. I'm fine.
- What do you think you're doing?
- S-- s-- s-- sorry!
Come on. See that? Sawako's being calm.
She's not getting all carried away
like you over some silly field trip.
And you need to apologize to her too.
S-- sorry about that. You good?
Yay.
-"Yay"?
Don't worry, be happy!
She's so excited.
- Let's take pics.
- Mm?
A whole bunch.
Shall we go shopping
for our trip, then?
We'll be together the whole time!
Four nights and five days straight!
We will? Really?
Ahh!
Kazehaya too.
Oh! We're getting split into groups today
for the upcoming trip.
Mm-hmm.
They're both
still acting the same.
Oh, Kazehaya.
At least start calling Sawako
by her first name already.
Mmm. Mmm.
Heya!
When the two of you are alone, do you
call each other by your first names, or...
I-- I don't see
how that's any of your business.
Sure, I get it. It's just that
I've been hearing these rumors
that you've already
met each other's parents and stuff,
so I was just curious.
How the hell did you find out?
You know how well-connected
I am, right? It's easy for me.
Wow! They're already meeting the parents.
What's wrong
with all the people around us?
Every one of them's
so insensitive and rude.
Four nights and five days.
I've never gotten to spend
that much time with them before.
Another first.
EPISODE 2
SCHOOL TRIP
Cool. It looks like
we've figured out our groups, then.
Yeah.
Hey.
You stopped coming by.
It's just because you're busy these days,
that's all.
With practice.
That's it?
Uh-huh.
Hm.
Since summer break,
everything just feels so awkward.
Everyone decide on a leader
for your group and report back.
- 'Kay!
- Leader? Should that be me, then? Or...
- I'll do it.
- Oh.
Huh? Really?
Awesome!
It's like you read my mind.
Leaders, meet me after school.
And no skipping out on this, got it?
Huh?!
Can...
...I wait for... you?
Mmm.
They really are
girlfriend and boyfriend, after all.
Mm.
- I'm heading to the meeting now.
- O-- okay.
- Sawako.
- Huh?
While you're waiting for Kazehaya
to finish up his meeting,
how about the three of us decide on
what we wanna do during our free time?
Can we?!
I wanna eat some soki soba.
And then buy that... that something-dama.
The ball thingies.
Oh, churadama. Huh?
Y-- Yui and Andy! Was that a confession?!
N-- no idea.
- There are new couples everywhere.
- Uh-huh.
Happens this time of year.
During festivals or class trips.
- All hail the queen.
- Help us, Master Sawako.
N-- no, don't ask me! I'm useless!
Hey... you're not gonna
hang out alone with Ryu, are you?
Huh?
- Like, during our free time.
- What? I'm confused.
Well, see, if things end up
working out between Andy and Yui,
and they're dating,
then they'll hang out together.
Mmm.
And you're going to be spending
lots of time alone with Kazehaya.
So, then, if Chizu and Ryu end up
spending their time together,
that'll just leave me and Joe, which means
we're stuck hanging together by default!
Now, you're not planning
on getting together with Ryu, right?
N-- no, of course not!
She-- she's not?
What's up though?
Like, is there anything new
going on lately?
Uh?
What? There is something, isn't there?
I mean, there may be something!
Or... or not!
Yeah, nothing going on at all!
Nothing of interest ever happened!
- Why are you being so weird, then?
- I'm not weird!
Everything is normal!
Do you have anyone you're interested in?
No. Not at all.
I've never had a crush
on anyone except Toru.
It didn't work out, but still,
I'm glad I got to tell him how I felt.
I've been curious.
What did you say when you confessed?
I just... said, "I, uh, like you."
- Sawako?
- Huh?!
Well, I said, "I like you"?
- Interesting. It was that simple, huh?
- Huh?
Well, then, what kinds of things do you
say to people when you confess to them?
Uh...
I've never told anyone I like them.
Really?!
Nope. Never.
When you finally get the chance to do it,
it'll feel great!
Huh? I'm good. That's the guy's job.
Wha-- Well that sucks.
Don't you want
to have a boyfriend, Yano?
Yeah, I suppose I do.
Don't know who though.
Huh?
On the hunt for a new boyfriend, Ayane?
Well, you could put me in the running.
I'm totally available right now.
- Nah, I'm good.
- Wow, that was cold.
And how are you doin'?
You seem good. Like, really happy.
- Oh, master!
- Come on now! That's no good!
Tears don't suit you, Sadako.
Let's change that.
You're so stiff.
What is this?
So did that bother you?
I didn't know you were the jealous type.
Oh, shut up!
Jealous?!
- You seem like a generally chilled guy.
- Hold on.
How did we end up in a position
where Kento's walking home with us?
For real. He's got some mad skills.
I was wondering what size luggage
we should use for the trip? This big?
Thiiiis big!
We should bring
an umbrella with us too, right?
I'm going to ask
for a little allowance increase.
They're inspecting our luggage.
I doubt Pin's gonna be strict.
Y-- Yano.
Uh?
- Do you think we could chat?
- Uh...
Wh-- what's up?
Hmm. Then, I guess I'll say it here.
- Here?!
- No way!
Uh, please go out with me!
Uh...
My name's Mogi. I'm from Class B.
Yano... you probably
don't know anything about me yet.
Do you remember
us bumping into each other?
- No.
- I figured.
But still, if you'd like...
Uh, we can take it slow.
Just start getting to know each other?
Okay.
Eh?
Let's go out.
Whaa!
Uh, we're going to be leaving
in just a bit.
Be sure to keep any valuables
you brought with you in your carry-on.
When you go through the security check,
please refrain from talking
and be as efficient as possible.
Once you've taken your seat on the plane,
be careful not to talk too loudly,
I don't want you bothering
the people around you.
-   We're flying!
- Finally.
- It's so cool!
- The day we've all waited for.
The start of our class trip!
- Sawa, snackies!
- Oh, thank you.
No, stop. Not like that.
Say, "Ah!" It's jerky!
- Ahh!
- Mmm!
But, anyways...
Check that out over there.
Like you said,
people confessing their feelings
to each other happens a lot during trips.
Or someone
calls you out to "talk." Every time.
Kuronuma. Here. You want one?
Oh, thank you!
D-- did I do something wrong?
I messed up, didn't I?
N-- no.
I'm going to go to the bathroom now.
Me too.
So this is where you're sitting.
Yeah. What about you?
Well, I'm over there.
- I can't wait for Okinawa.
- Yeah, same.
Right, I'll go first.
Looks like things
are going pretty well between them.
But it's kinda awkward.
I mean, this whole time, I sorta figured
Ayane and I would get together.
What? Well, good for them.
Whatever it takes.
Yeah, sure.
But still, there are other ways
it can happen!
Huh? What the heck, Kento?
What's he trying to say?
Yano's boyfriend is...
Mogi, right?
Are things going okay between them?
Yeah. Seems like it.
Are you going to
date him, Yano-chin?
Yeah.
He seems like a good guy, so why not?
Besides, the class trip
might be even more fun this way.
I... I think it will be fun.
Yeah, it's going to be so much fun!
It's Okinawa!
Whoa!
Whoa, the humidity.
I feel like I could swim in this air.
There's no mistaking it.
We're not up north anymore!
We finally made it!
So what do we have after this?
We get a little time to rest,
have some dinner, and then bath time.
- We should go check out the hotel.
- Okay.
Oh, Sawako.
Did you bring the underwear we got?
Oh. Uh... yes, I did.
- Kazehaya!
- Uh... mm-hmm?
Ya know, us girls, we went shopping
the other day to buy panties.
Including Sawako.
- Uh... Uh... That's nice?
- Kazehaya, that's not all.
She got... side-tie ones.
Why would...
What am I supposed to do
with that information, huh?
Thanks for waiting.
- What's up? What was that all about?
- Nothing!
- You better not tell anyone else.
- I won't, obviously!
I've never seen you without a skirt on.
I wanted to wear something
easy to move around in,
since we'll be active.
- Does it look weird?
- No, not at all.
- You thinkin' about--
- No, I'm not!
Don't ask! And don't look!
Here's the thing
about panties, Sawako.
A woman doesn't wear them
just for herself.
It's just underwear.
Women wear them
to pump themselves up. That's all.
You only say that 'cause you've
not needed them in that way yet, Chizu.
What's that mean?!
What an adult conversation.
What about you, Yano-chin?
How's Mogi-cchi?
Oh, we're planning to meet each other
tomorrow evening.
Then we're planning to walk around
Kokusai-dori, just the two of us.
- Is that cool?
- Yeah, fine, go ahead.
Sawako, you should
hang out with Kazehaya.
Wha-- what about me?
Let's see...
You've got Ryu, right? And Joe.
I knew it!
I knew this would happen,
so I can't be upset!
But still!
- So, uh...
- Mmm?
You two... would call this conversation
a heart-to-heart between girls,
wouldn't you?
- Of course.
- What's up? Did something happen?
Uh, it's just, there's something
I wanted to ask you, Ayane.
What is it?
You can ask me anything you want.
I... I was wondering
when did you...
you first start having feelings for Mogi?
Huh?! Wait, do you mean
you started liking him?
Really? Like, when?!
Well... I wouldn't go
out of my way to tell everyone...
We're already dating.
You're always like this!
It's so frustrating!
You're so pushy with other people!
But then you pretty much
never talk about yourself!
I get it! Next time something happens,
I'll tell you.
- You mean it?
- Yes.
I want to drink something cold.
Oh, and fizzy too.
- I wonder what they have here?
- Tea for me.
- Oh.
- It's them.
Oh.
What's up? You just finish your bath too?
Your hair, Ryu. Sea urchin.
That's not true. Sheesh.
- Hmm?
- Mm?
Huh?! But what if I wanna
choose my own drink?!
Then, go right ahead. Pick one.
Let's see...
Um, how about... I go with a... Maybe?
This one.
You can buy some ice cream
for me as payback.
Huh?! That's way more expensive!
What would you like?
A Jasmine tea sounds good to me.
OKINAWAN JASMINE TEA
As soon as I find my wallet...
- I remember this happening before.
- Huh?
Huh?! The coffee!
Here. This one's on me.
This isn't my normal routine.
I'm living my life outside of school.
But Kazehaya is here.
Thank you for that.
How nice! Did he say, "free"?
Tell me where I can get some of that
free jasmine tea for myself.
You're a menace
to society, Yano.
So how far have you gone with Sadako?
Give me the deets!
You must've kissed by now
or at least you held hands?
- Shut up.
- You suck! Bleurgh!
- Huh?
- Uh-oh.
Is the teacher here to check in on us?
I'll get it.
You'd call us friends,
wouldn't you, Ryu?
Sure.
Ha! So, yeah, what do you
and Sadako do on your dates anyway?
- Dude, leave me alone!
- Ryu?
- Huh?
- It's a girl from Class C.
Huh?
Rise and shine!
- Huh!
- That's right! We're on
the class trip right now, aren't we? Huh?
- I'm getting your wake-up face!
- Wha-- what?
- Oooh! Yeah! Nice!
- How are you so loud?
- Your turn now!
- Knock it off.
Wow! I woke up inside a hotel.
And my friends' faces
were the very first thing I saw.
I get to eat breakfast with everyone!
And the person I like is here.
G'morning!
Good morning.
So did you sleep okay?
Honestly, I was too excited to sleep.
Things like this
don't usually happen to me.
Same for me. Everyone kept talking.
Joe was more annoying than usual.
That's just him. Always.
What a surprise.
I'm your tour guide, Higa.
I'm so glad you're all here with me today.
Boom! Kyu! Bang!
The pleasure is all mine.
For real?
-   Well, this'll be a ride.
- How friendly.
Group photo time! Over here!
This way.
- Did you hear what he said?
-"This way"!
That was so good!
Come stand where you belong. With me!
- You are so annoying!
- Come on. Go ahead.
All right, everyone!
Look over here for me, okay?
I've never taken a group photo
quite like this.
Make sure you all stay with your groups!
And meet back at the bus on time!
Care to see the manatees with me?
Oh, I've seen them. Many times.
Pretty!
That shrimp is huge!
- Wow, there's so many.
- Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
Kuronuma.
Right there. Look, there's a whale shark.
- Oh! D-- did you take one?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh! It's coming over here. Okay, smile!
What is going on?
I'm not used to posing for photos.
And, if I think about it,
Kazehaya's in some of these.
But only in the background
or corner of some of the group pictures.
I haven't actually
taken any of just him yet.
I'm so nervous.
M-- maybe I should try it now?
You looked over at me!
- Obviously.
- Y-- yeah, you're right.
Yay!
That manta ray just now
looked exactly like me!
So awesome!
It's the bottom!
It's huge!
I'm so happy.
I've made so many new memories.
Truly happy.
The aquarium is the bomb!
It's so much fun!
- I took tons of photos too.
- Oh! Yay! Let me see 'em!
Look at Joe's face! Idiot!
- Do you wanna see ours too?
- Yeah. Show me.
There are... so many of me.
These are everyone's memories...
and I'm there too.
Wow! It really does
look like an elephant!
You're right.
The ocean sure is beautiful.
Yano?!
Wha-- what are you doing
standing out here holding a parasol?!
You're so damn loud.
I'm protecting my skin from UV rays.
Why? Did you come all the way
to Okinawa just to pick up girls?
There was the aquarium, right?
And the pineapples...
And then chillin'
at the hotel's private beach!
But today was the day
we were looking forward to the most!
Hold on.
So, that means we're almost done, then?
Like, it's all downhill from here?
Either way, I can't wait
until our free time tonight.
The beach and the stars!
Speaking of, I promised Mogi-cchi
I'd meet up with him there.
Oh yeah? How naughty of you!
In what way?
No, thank you! Give up!
Leave me alone!
Even when you're angry, you're so cute!
Stop following me!
I was on my way to the beach too!
What a coincidence!
- I'm not going anymore!
- - No, wait!
- You run so fast!
K-- Kurumi? What was that?
Well, according to my research,
Ume's current reputation is
"the girl who gives it to you straight."
She's been gathering
quite the following too.
I'm confused but impressed.
Seriously though,
Kurumi really is popular.
Chigusa found out that
eight people in our class
have been confessed to.
Amazing. She's not even
in our class anymore.
Wait. Does that include me?
Oh yeah, probably.
Guess that makes nine, then.
- Huh?
- What are you talking about?
You're forgetting to include your
childhood friend in that list of yours!
Ryu! Someone confessed to him yesterday!
Huh?
But, what? Is that true?
- He also rejected her on the spot.
- What?
The whole thing
went down last night.
She came to our room
and asked to talk to him.
So that's how it is.
He doesn't want to tell me about it.
I see. He said no... of course.
My eyes are only for Chizuru.
It's a secret.
The ocean's
completely different down here.
Y-- yeah.
The sand is so white,
and the water's so blue.
Right?
Now, Kazehaya,
please take care of Sawako.
Good care, good care--
Now, remember,
to conduct yourself with propriety.
You're still children
who can't support yourselves.
And children
should interact like children.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, I know that, okay?!
Oh, I, uh... I'm sorry!
Uh, n-- no,
I-- I didn't mean you.
What did I just see?
Aw, cute!
- Uh, Kento?
- What's up?
Ah, Yano!
- Are you still free tonight?
- Yeah.
Later.
- Where's a good place to meet up?
- Oh, uh, where we said before.
- Sure. See you later.
- See ya.
- Awesome, man.
- Good job!
- Good night.
- Mm-hmm.
What are you doing?
It's time to go to sleep now.
Back to your room.
Oh, it's just you scared me.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm your homeroom teacher, remember?
So what about it?
You were supposed to be our chaperone,
but you just came here to flirt!
That's none of your business!
What does it matter
to you anyway?
To think this world's filled
with these poor excuses for men.
- So, hey.
- Huh?
Have you been in love before?
Random. Well, yeah.
Uh...
So what's wrong with her?
Y-- you k-- kissed?!
Chill out. You asked me how things went.
- So I gave you the rundown.
- They kissed! No wonder they took so long!
I knew it!
I had a feeling something was up!
Calm down! Seriously.
K-- kissing?
They did that?!
H-- how grown up!
Now what?
Oh, it's, uh... nothing.
I'll say this now.
That you're going to do it too, Sawako!
N-- no way!
Huh? You won't?
- Yes, you will!
- I... I will?!
You're absolutely
going to kiss him!
I... I am?!
- Or maybe not.
- I... I'm not?!
Which one is it?
Shota, are you sick?
I... don't think...
Won't my... heart explode?
It won't.
Lucky! It's not fair!
Oh yeah,
when I was gone, what did you guys do?
Go visit Kazehaya and Ryu?
Huh? Why would we do that?
We just had a girls' hang!
A kiss?
J... just a dream!
What's wrong?
- Ah, shut up!
- N-- nothing!
- What time is it?
- I'm totally fine!
- What's going on?
- D-- don't worry!
Everyone! Let's take a photo, okay?
Say cheese!
What d'you think?
Which class sounds good?
- Hmm, lemme think.
- It's hard.
Okay. How about we say what
we wanna do out loud at the same time?
Yeah, good idea.
Hey, Joe, check it out.
They're sure having fun.
- Totally! Even Sadako!
- One, two...
- Sanshin!
- Ceramics!
HUH?
'Kay, Sawako, have fun with that.
We're going to do sanshin.
No, actually, I want to do sanshin too!
No, you should go
and do your ceramics painting.
We came all the way to Okinawa, after all.
We should all do what we want.
Yeah, but what I want to do is keep
having fun with whatever you're doing!
You should be
having fun with that.
Hmm?
- Wha-- No, I can't!
- Huh?
Oh, she says that she can't.
No, but that's not what I meant to say!
- Okay, but you know what? I...
- Did they team up?
I... I can't stop thinking about
that dream I had!
By the way, Kuronuma,
I remember you telling my dad before
that you like drawing and stuff.
So do you draw often?
No, it's just a casual hobby.
I'm not particularly
good at it or anything.
Huh? Show me.
Next time, maybe I'll ask you to draw me.
KAZEHAYA-KUN
You're getting souvenirs
for your parents, right?
- Have you decided what yet?
- Y-- yeah.
I'm buying some snow salt for my mom.
Maybe a few other things
if I find something I know they'll like.
I was thinking of getting one of those
Hawaiian-print shirts for my dad.
That's so him!
That kind of shirt would look good
on your dad too, don't you think?
Maybe you could get him one as well.
Uh... then maybe I'll buy one
that matches the one you're getting
for your dad?
Why would you do that?
I'm done.
Mine's kind of sloppy,
but I think it fits my vibe.
You think I could see it?
He's good!
How's yours going?
You're being so careful.
Uh...
For some reason,
it ended up looking like Mr. Arai.
OKINAWA'S DISTILLED ALCOHOL DRINK
AWAMORI
Ga-haa!
Wish we could just leave
that thing in Okinawa.
Are you really sure it's okay
if I keep this for myself?
Yeah. You gave me yours, so we're even.
I... I wonder if I should have.
I mean, it's kind of an abomination.
No, I'm glad. I'll put it on display.
It was an awesome memory.
- Oh.
- Fortunes?
FORTUNE
GREAT BLESSING
"Great blessing"?!
Wow! That's so awesome.
And I got "middle."
"You will be released
from your previous suffering,
and your luck is going to improve."
You think it's true?
"Romance. What you're worried about
will be resolved soon."
"And your love will continue growing."
So it says.
"Love... will continue growing."
"Choose someone you deeply respect,
and tell them you love them. Promising."
I wonder when it started?
In the summer, there was still space
between us when we walked.
But now, we're so close
we sometimes bump into each other.
- Oh, there they are! Sawa!
- Where's Ryu and the guys?
They all went over there
to check out the goats.
- Ah. I'll go say hi.
- Okay.
- Oh, by the way, we got some goat milk.
- It's goat milk?
Stronger than a cow's, but good!
It's what they drink
in Heidi, Girl of the Alps.
Y-- Yoshida.
- Oh.
- Mmm?
Huh?
I... I was wondering
how you felt about Sanada?
Oh yeah?
Say what you want directly.
You're not even being
straight up with me right now.
So you're just gonna ask me
some vague question first?
That doesn't make any sense.
What do you really want?
Chizu's in full-on battle mode right now.
Just watch.
We're witnessing the other side
of the lovable goofball we know.
- I told him I like him.
- So?
- But I was rejected.
Then I asked him
if there's someone else he likes.
There... was.
My first thought was
that maybe it was you,
since you two are always together.
So?
What if it is me?
- Why would that matter to you?
- Huh?
Tell me. Why'd you bring all your friends?
Why are you asking me all this?
What is the point here?
What reaction could I possibly give you
that would make you happy?!
Uh, hold on, Chizu.
So mean.
It's just that, if you don't like Sanada,
I wanted to let him know
he shouldn't hang out with you so much.
That's none of your business!
You've no right to say anything!
- S... Sae!
- So mean!
Ch... Chizu.
- Huh? What's wrong?
- Tell me!
- Hey!
- Shut up!
What did I do now?!
She's pissed!
It's not my fault, I swear,
but she's big mad!
All right.
I have plans to meet up with someone.
Be back later.
'Kay. See you later.
- Sorry, Sawa.
- Huh?
Is it cool if I leave early too?
I could actually use some fresh air.
Uh, of course.
Don't worry about me.
Just finish drying your hair, okay?
Uh... thank you!
- Taco rice is a different kind of taco.
- It's not octopus?
- Ayane!
- Uh?
Well, let's eat!
- What's up? You waiting for someone?
- Uh, yeah.
How nice.
Sure makes me wish I had a girlfriend.
It looks like you have
tons of girlfriends to have fun with.
Those are friends.
But what I'm looking for is a lover.
Gotcha.
What's Mogi-cchi like anyway?
What kinds of things
do the two of you talk about?
What do we talk about?
How's that information
any of your business whatsoever?
I just wanted some tea.
But I'm happy for you.
Did you wait long?
- No.
- And your friends, are they cool?
Yeah.
Sorry.
- Hmm!
- What's with you?
You've been acting weird.
I heard a girl told you she liked you
and that you rejected her!
But you didn't tell me anything about it!
Why would I?
It's none of your business.
Then don't send her right to me
so it's my problem!
Work it out with her,
and deal with it on your own!
She rapid-fired
a whole lot of nonsense at me too!
Y'know, that there's someone you like.
You wanna know?
No, thanks. It's none of my business.
Ayane forgot to bring her phone with her.
I'm glad I happened to find it
before I left the bath.
I wonder if the two of them
are back in our room by now?
Chizu looked kind of sad when she left.
She tried to hide it though.
Oh, right.
I should go buy some shikuwasa juice.
Oh.
Did you just finish up
with your bath as well?
Oh, that's a coincidence.
I was the last one out of the girls'.
- Huh? Where's everyone else?
- Uh.
It wasn't a coincidence.
I've been waiting for you.
I waited for a while,
but you didn't show up.
So I thought that maybe
you already went back to your room.
In fact, I was getting ready to leave,
but then I saw you.
- Oh! I'm sorry I made you wait.
- Don't be. It's okay.
It's fine.
I just...
wanted to see you for a little bit...
so I'm glad.
Uh...
I got my wish.
I sat down so close to him
that if one of us moved at all,
we'd bump into each other.
If I were to... look at his face...
my heart might actually explode.
What do I do?
I... can't look away.
His body feels warm.
I've never heard a sound like this
come out of me before.
Not even a millimeter.
Hey. Close your eyes.
I... I'm sorry.
I forgot my phone and just realized.
Y-- your phone?!
I-- I-- I have it here with me!
- J-- just give me a sec to find it!
- Uh... Oh, really? I'm sorry.
P-- please don't worry about it at all!
- Here!
- Oh, uh, okay, thanks.
Cool. Continue.
Contin--
- Sorry!
- Uh?
Man... it's time for bed.
Y-- yeah.
Sorry, Kuronuma.
See you tomorrow.
It's okay.
I won't tell anybody.
Just now,
if Ayane hadn't come when she did...
I'm sorry, Sawako.
No, please. It's okay, really it is.
Honest.
Yeah, so anyway, did you go see him?
I mean Mogi.
Yeah. And then I noticed
I didn't have my phone.
Ah. Gotcha.
Mmm. Makes sense. Yeah.
I can still remember...
the way he feels.
Sorry.
Mm-hmm
Me too.
I've been kinda worried
about my friend,
so I'm gonna head back early tonight.
Oh. Okay.
We'll meet for tomorrow's free time, then.
Oh, my phone's missing.
Is it in the changing room?
Huh? Really?
But... what if it really is gone?
How am I supposed to get a hold of you?
I'll figure it out.
Huh? It's dark.
Uh?
Why are you sitting in the dark like this?
- I'm turning the lights on.
- 'Kay. And welcome back.
- That's interesting.
- Huh?
I thought you hated drinks
that were all sweet and sugary.
SUPER SWEET
Yeah, I do!
Huh? Seriously?
Maybe... it would have been
better if I stayed with her.
I could tell
she was feeling sad from the start.
But... I couldn't think
of anyone but myself.
What's wrong with me?
- Chizu.
- Mmm?
Take this.
SHIKWASA JUICE
Thank you.
What's the matter?
Something happen?
Uh...
So the free time
we have on the fourth day,
we're spending that with our boyfriends.
- What about me?!
- Chizu, you've got Ryu.
No.
It's nothing.
Hey.
So that's where you were.
Where are Joe and Andy?
Um... they said they were gonna
visit the girls for a little bit.
I see.
Uh...
is something wrong?
Not really. What about you though, Ryu?
Even if I told you,
it's not gonna change anything.
It's not that.
You don't usually drink those, right?
The sweet ones?
SUPER SWEET
MADE WITH WASANBON SUGAR
I thought I was drinking water.
Seriously?
I was being so careful.
I totally lost control.
Somehow,
it all feels like a dream.
Did that actually happen in real life?
But, the feelings are still with me.
And tomorrow...
how am I supposed to face him?
There aren't any activities
planned for today.
Just don't cause trouble for anyone.
If you get lost, then contact us.
That's it.
Get outta here!
Where should we go?
What should we do? Huh?
- Hey! And tell me! What's out there?
- All right. Let's go.
Bye.
Last night, before I feel asleep...
...I did a lot of thinking.
Hey, Chizu. If things are feeling
too awkward between you and Sanada,
then how about you spend your free time
with us tomorrow?
That's fine with me.
I'll just have to skip
hanging out with Mogi-cchi.
I am super disappointed about it though.
Huh!
I can't do that.
Ayane will change her plans too.
She's too considerate.
I don't wanna make her do that!
Oh! What should I do?
If it's too awkward,
spend your free time with me.
Are you purposely avoiding me now?
- Huh?! No! I'm not, at all!
- Gotcha. Never mind. It's fine.
My bad.
Sorry, Kuronuma.
I ended up overthinking.
And I wasn't able
to say anything to Chizu at all!
Uh-- Should... we go?
Uh, y-- yeah
Huh? What's wrong with you two?
You look like you're trying
to do the damn robot or something.
Wha-- No. What are you talking about?!
Well, it doesn't matter to me. Whatever!
Here's the thing. Listen.
You can't lose control!
That came out wrong.
I meant, don't act crazy.
- What, are you dying?
- Not yet, at least.
Huh! Hey, Ayane! Spending your free time
with the boyfriend?
I guess so.
Kento! C'mon, let's go.
'Kay!
There's more distance.
Did I... cause it without realizing?
There's our two lovebirds!
- Hi!
- Takahashi!
Mmmm? Ahhhh! Uhhh?
Heh.
Oh no, this just won't do.
Both of you are so nervous
and on edge today.
Have you two taken any pictures
or anything together?
N-- no, we haven't taken any yet.
There's a super cute spot over there
that's perfect for couples
to take photos together.
I could take some for you!
Oh, uh... thank you,
but you don't have to do all that.
C'mon?! What are you talking about?
Tell me.
Does that mean you don't care at all
about making Sadako happy as your partner?
I-- I'm already really happy, so...
Kuronuma, let's take some pictures!
Look at that,
he wants to make the girl he loves happy!
Yay! What a man.
You're gonna need to stop talking
like that. Seriously.
Mmmm!
Mmm! Oh wow!
You've got a really nice camera.
Just take the picture. Please.
Huh? What?
I didn't know those two were together!
Sorry, something just came up.
Perfect timing!
- Could you take over?
- Huh?
Hmm.
I'm gonna take a photo of the prince
of Kitahoro High School
and the happiest moment
of his entire life!
Why are you like this?!
POTTERY STREET
- These shisa are adorable.
- I think I like those ones more.
Huh?
The ones on the left are way cuter!
- So, hey...
- Huh?
- It's Mogi!
Hey! Over here!
Uh...
Don't worry about me, you go ahead.
I'll do some browsing around here.
I've been wanting to shop anyway.
Oh... if you're sure.
Later!
What's goin' on?
Have you been hangin' around here?
Hmm.
Wow! This is a pig?!
The fish are amazing!
- Everything's amazing!
- Joe is always so fricking annoying!
But, I'm actually glad he's here.
I didn't think you were gonna come.
Huh? Just because I didn't want to make
Yano-chin and Sawako change their plans!
So don't be dumb! Ugh!
Me being here has nothing to do
with you, okay? It's all for my girlies!
Mm-hmm.
But still,
being alone together probably isn't
what either of us wants right now.
At least, that's how I feel.
And Ryu's probably the same.
- Chizuru.
- Mmm?
Ice cream.
Uh?
You owe me.
HANDMADE ITALIAN GELATO
Yum! Yum!
What is happening?!
So good.
How are you able to get me
to buy you ice cream at a time like this?
Well, you promised me.
What the-- Not!
Oh, that's not fair! How come you didn't
buy ice cream for me too, Yoshida?
Why would you ever think
I was supposed to buy you ice cream?
It doesn't make any sense,
no matter how I think about it!
Oh, hey, Ryu.
So why'd you end up
turning down that girl from Class C?
Is there somebody else that you like?
- Hmm.
- No way, really? Who is it, who?!
It's none of your business, Joe.
- What's your deal?! Just tell me, c'mon!
- Yep.
- And it's none of my business either.
- No.
Okay, but why?!
That's right.
It's none of my business.
And he won't tell me anyway.
I thought... I knew everything
there was to know about Ryu.
But he likes someone.
And I had to hear that for the first time
from a girl I barely even know.
But why?
He knows that I like Toru,
so why can't he tell me who he likes.
I guess it's different.
Ryu found out who I like on his own.
I'm not the one who told him.
But... I guess childhood friends
are just like this.
But still...
Still...
I was wondering
how you felt about Sanada?
If you don't like Sanada,
I wanted to let him know
he shouldn't hang out with you so much.
That's none of your business!
You have no right to say anything!
The two of us have always...
But... am I right?
Maybe I'm the only one
who thinks that way.
Maybe it's really just
none of my business.
Maybe I don't deserve to feel this
angry at Ryu.
Maybe this entire time,
he's had someone he's liked,
and I just didn't know.
One day,
is he going to start dating someone?
This baseball idiot?
Okay! I'm gonna go get seconds!
Oh wow! So what do we have here?
Ooo, and what's this one? Mmm!
Oh, hey! What a coincidence!
What are you guys up to?
- Whoa!
- It's Joe!
So, this is probably
not gonna end well, right?
- Maybe it's fate?
- C'mon!
- This is good.
- Mmm.
This one's good too.
Damn right.
Don't you feel a little awkward?
When I got upset at you yesterday,
do you have any idea why?
- Are you listening?
- Yeah.
It made me happy...
...that you cared.
That you were at least
a little interested in... who I might like.
It made me happy.
Since that person
was always you.
Thank you for shopping with us!
Where did everyone go?
Are you serious?
C'mon, I was so sure!
You went from dating to kissing,
just like that, ya know?
I thought everything
was moving along quick and easy.
We're talkin' about Yano.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
I guess I just set
my expectations too high is all.
- What about today?
- No way.
- We haven't even held hands yet today.
- Is this what you want?
Uh?
H-- hi, Yano!
What's going on?
So it's like that?
Are you kidding me? Gimme a break!
I actually thought
you were a trustworthy guy.
I know what
you're thinking, but Mogi isn't a bad guy.
Nah, I think you just got the wrong idea!
For sure! It's just that
he got his hopes up about you, y'know?
And got disappointed without ever asking
if I'm comfortable doing things like that?
- That's skeevy.
- You're right!
Uh...
Y-- Yano.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
But... I don't feel like
continuing this relationship anymore.
I understand.
See ya.
Uh... Yano!
For real, I am sorry.
Were you trying to
tell me something before?
Sorry, about yesterday.
Nope.
- That's so cute!
- I wanna take it home!
Hey, you've gotta stop them
before they really get outta hand.
Huh?
Huh? Hey, Kento.
I've gotta go. Sorry.
Huh? Where are you going?!
Ayane!
What's wrong?
Kento.
What are you doing here alone?
Where's Mogi-cchi?
We just broke up.
What happened?
Now that I think about it,
no wonder.
What things
do the two of you talk about?
In conversations,
he'd always just go along
with whatever I was talking about.
There was never any substance.
And the day we started dating,
he didn't even walk home with me.
I bet after that, he went straight
to report it to his friends.
He never...
he never actually liked me at all.
I'm fine.
I really am okay.
Nothing's wrong.
Even though we kissed...
I-- I was wondering,
when did you
first start having feelings for Mogi?
You've got it all wrong, Sawako.
We aren't the same.
It's not like it is for you.
Where anyone could tell
how much your heart was racing
with just a quick glance.
Because I never liked him at all.
Kento, you've had a lot of girlfriends
until now, haven't you?
You... you make it sound
like it's a bad thing.
But have you ever
fallen in love with someone?
Have I...
Well, of course,
that's why I started dating them.
I haven't.
I've never fallen in love with anyone.
I've never dated someone
because I like them.
That's why... I can't...
Ayane, hey.
I can't be like Sawako and Chizu.
It's... just that
when I see people pour their hearts out
or be on the receiving end,
it gives me hope that I could be the same.
I thought maybe
he was showing that kind of vulnerability
with me when he confessed.
And that maybe
I could come to love him in time.
That's what I thought.
Don't get me wrong. I don't...
I don't feel sad
or anything like that.
I said it's not like that.
How come... you're not saying anything?
All right! Everyone here?
Time for us to fly back to Hokkaido!
Let's hurry up and get home already!
Huh? What's goin' on
with you, Pin?
Yesterday, you said
you were never goin' home.
I heard he asked Higa
for a long-distance relationship,
and she turned him down.
Really?
Do you think
it's gonna be cold when we get back?
- I hope not.
- You're always cold, Yano-chin.
Well, I don't like being too hot either.
You just need to learn
how to deal with being uncomfy.
Since that person... was always you.
There's never been anyone else.
Ryu, I've...
never thought of you like that.
Yeah.
I know.
For all of us...
it's the start of a new season.